

Notes: d24d6c8c91bfa4a486c4612097dbe342288d9566

1. set a max cap to the route so to prevent color - palette -color -pelete circular back track
2. Improved analytics, decrease resource consumption, and offer better more fine grained control
3. fixed Color palette saved but button not reflecting state bug
4. remvoe hex and name copy butto, and favourite button of palette in color details
5. add color tint effect to color detail screen
6. Fixed tonal elevation so the settings page appears better.
7. add gaps to palette screen header
8. Change color preview: recent circular, saved square, palette vertical list
9. Use fancy waterCard for Start Picking and Pick From album screen
10. Change colors to horizontal scroll